# **Anders Jensen**

Full Stack Developer

## PROFILE

Software engineer with over four years of experience building web based applications for Booz Allen Hamilton. Developed various projects for company leadership and for use at the firm's Innovation office and worked as part of a software development team supporting government clients.

804.335.6054

jensenal27@gmail.com

jensenal27.github.io

**Active Secret Clearance** 

# EDUCATION

### Bachelor of Arts, English Literature

Old Dominion University / 2016

# SKILLS

# Development

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, NodeJS

#### Frameworks & Libraries

Angular, React, Spring, D3.js

#### **Databases**

PostgreSQL

#### Other

Git, Jira, Docker

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Full Stack Developer**

Booz Allen Hamilton, (April 2021 - Present)

- + Build out Front End features and Back End endpoints for latest version of DIBNet
- + Reduce Front End duplicate code by creating several reusable components
- + Write Back End unit tests and develop Front End E2E test scripts to maintain high level of test coverage
- + Tech Used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Angular, TypeScript, Java, Spring Boot, Docker

## Workplace Experience Manager, Innovation Center

Booz Allen Hamilton, (January 2018 - March 2021)

- + Develop, modify, and update Virtual Events Calendar to showcase upcoming and past events as part of the Innovation Center's virtual events strategy
- + Create prototypes for upcoming business projects to present to leadership
- + Design, modify, develop, write, and implement software systems to facilitate employee and guest interaction with technology throughout the innovation center
- + Develop interactive dashboard to display Center metrics data to firm leadership
- + Manage quality control by maintaining 100K budget and managing vendor relationships
- + Act as liaison to CBRE facilities leadership representing Booz Allen Hamilton's first innovation office: The Innovation Center
- + Tech Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SharePoint, D3.js

# Logistics Coordinator, Conference Center

Booz Allen Hamilton, (July 2016 - December 2017)

- + Execute meeting and event logistics and planning in three conference center locations
- + Assist with the implementation of new firmwide tool used for scheduling meeting and event space and workspace
- + Lead information sessions on-site and via teleconference for internal staff during launch